Free agent defensive [music] lineman
Sebastian Joseph Day.
>> You know, they move him all around the
line. He plays really hard. High motor
[music] guy. I think he's a perfect fit.
Welcome to Pittsburgh. You grew up on
the other side of Pennsylvania. Had you
been to Pittsburgh not football related
before? Um no, not football related.
I've been to Pittsburgh to play.
Yeah, and that's that's about it.
>> That's about it. Do you call Aaron
Donald and ask him what he knows about
Pittsburgh or what you should do?
>> yeah, that's Funny, I'm actually I took
a picture cuz of his facility. Yes. I
took a picture. I'm about to send it
over to him cuz uh it's awesome just to
see
uh what he's done and being from here
and what it means to him. So, yeah, he's
my guy. I'm definitely going to give him
a ring and ask him [music] where to go,
the spots and whatnot. What was it like
earlier in your career playing with
someone like Aaron Donald who is what he
is now? Yeah, I mean um
words can't describe what Aaron means to
me as a as a friend and [music] um
obviously as his teammate, he taught me
so much.
He's such a good human being, man. I
feel like that's something that's not
talked about. He's always talking about
how dominant he is as a football player,
but who he is as a human being and how
much he loves people and he pours back
into people that love the game and
people that don't love the game, either.
He's just a great great individual and
it's really been amazing to be able to
call him a friend.
In terms of the defensive line, do you
have a specific spot that you like a
little bit more than another one?
Honestly, no. Um
that's just funny. I think I think what
makes me a little unique is that I legit
play anywhere. [music]
I started my career, like I said,
playing next to Aaron at nose. Mhm. Then
when I went to the Chargers, played more
three. Now with the Titans, I played
more five tech, six tech, which is more
outside, you know, [music] um on the
tackle, outside the tackle. So, I just
feel like I pride myself on just being
able [music] to
you know, do it all and be able to just
play from anywhere and get and you know,
get the job done. I don't I don't
consider myself flashy. I don't consider
myself pretty. I don't try to be pretty.
You know, bring your hard hat and your
lunch pail and just get it done, you
know? Sounds like Pittsburgh.
That's that's what Pittsburgh is. What
do you know about Cam Heyward, some of
the guys that are on that line here
>> Yeah, I mean
>> Yeah, I mean Cam, I mean, Cam's a Hall
of Famer himself, man. You know, his
body of work that he's been able to put
out is just amazing to see and to see
that him still going at his age is is
tremendous. Man, I've nothing but,
[music] you know, just respect for him
and his game.
Um obviously, you know, T.J. Watt, he's
a dog. He wins from anywhere and I know
they got a bunch of young players, too,
that are really establishing themselves
as well. So, you know, if I could just
[music] come in and, you know, pass some
wisdom down and be a help wherever I can
and just get the job done wherever they
want me to and that's the plan.
Hopefully, you know, we could do great
things this season cuz I see it I see
the vision. What has Patrick Graham told
you just about what he sees in you and
how you would fit in his system? It was
all [music] really positive conversation
and um
things to look forward to and I'm really
excited um the way he's [music] going to
use me and the way he sees sees my
skillset and what I could do to help.
Perfect. Thank you. Yeah, [music] no
problem.